# Written by: Christopher Gholmieh
# Image:
image:
  # Title:
  title: "Linux Probing"

  # User:
  user: "prober"


# Vulnerabilities:
vulnerabilities:
  # Forensics:
  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the file that contains hashed passwords located in /etc? Please enter the full path of the file!"

    # Answer:
    answer: "/etc/shadow"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-1.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "1"

    # Points:
    points: 5

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the file that contains user records in /etc? Please enter the full path of the file!"

    # Answer:
    answer: "/etc/passwd"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-2.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "2"

    # Points:
    points: 5

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the unique machine id for this Linux system?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "TODO: Do this!"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-3.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "3"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the name of the bootloader on this Linux system (all lowercase)?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "grub"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-4.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "4"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the name of the user with the EUID of 0 (all lowercase)?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "root"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-5.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "5"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the UID of the user prober?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "1000"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-6.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "6"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the name of the user that should not be on this system?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "gwashington"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-7.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "7"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the permission (in octal format, e.g 777) of /etc/passwd?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "777"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-8.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "8"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the name of the malicious package located on this system?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "john"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-9.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "9"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the full path of the plaintext password file located on this system?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "/etc/firewall.txt"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-10.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "10"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the hostname of this system?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "WHSCyberPatriots"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-11.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "11"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the full path of the malicious script being ran through crontabs?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "/usr/share/malicious_backdoor.py"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-12.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "12"

    # Points:
    points: 5 

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the full path of the mp4 file hidden on this system?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "/home/jmuskington/Music/my_favorite_song.mp4"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-13.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "13"

    # Points:
    points: 5

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "Who is the owner of the file /etc/hickory?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "/home/jmuskington/Music/my_favorite_song.mp4"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-14.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "14"

    # Points:
    points: 5

  - vulnerability:
    # Type:
    type: "Forensics"

    # Question:
    question: "What is the name of the vulnerable service running through systemd?"

    # Answer:
    answer: "nginx"

    # Path:
    path: "/home/prober/Desktop/Forensics-Question-15.txt"

    # Number:
    number: "15"

    # Points:
    points: 5
